ezinequeen.com 2014-03-25

# 

                                              Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our
newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name,
e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however,
visit our site anonymously.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART
cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the
Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content
network privacy policy.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
; To improve our website
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we
receive from you.
; To improve customer service
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and
support needs.
; To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to
any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express
purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
; To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and
updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates,
related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include
detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
              Ali International LLC | 20701 N. Scottsdale Rd., Ste 107-412, Scottsdale, AZ 85255
   Toll-free: 888-484-5559 | Fax: 877-742-8056 | Email: Info@AliBrown.com | © 2014 Ali International LLC

How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information
when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via
Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only
accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep
the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.)
will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to process recurring transactions.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard
drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems
to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, keep track of
advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can
offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent,
or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn
your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place
orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable
information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website,
conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information
confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to
comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for
marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our
website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore
have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless,
we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
              Ali International LLC | 20701 N. Scottsdale Rd., Ste 107-412, Scottsdale, AZ 85255
   Toll-free: 888-484-5559 | Fax: 877-742-8056 | Email: Info@AliBrown.com | © 2014 Ali International LLC

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act),
we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and
services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Terms of Service
Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of
liability governing the use of our website at
http://AliBrown.com/pdf/Terms-of-Service.pdf.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date
below.
This policy was last modified on 01/01/2014.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information
below.
http://www.AliBrown.com
20701 N. Scottsdale Road, Ste. 107-412
Scottsdale, AZ 85255
Legal@AliBrown.com
888-484-5559
               Ali International LLC | 20701 N. Scottsdale Rd., Ste 107-412, Scottsdale, AZ 85255
    Toll-free: 888-484-5559 | Fax: 877-742-8056 | Email: Info@AliBrown.com | © 2014 Ali International LLC
